<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daily Quotes</string>
    <string name="day_1">day1</string>
    <string name="day_2">day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">day 17</string>
    <string name="day_18">day 18</string>
    <string name="day_19">day 19</string>
    <string name="day_20">day 20</string>
    <string name="day_21">day 21</string>
    <string name="day_22">day 22</string>
    <string name="day_23">day 23</string>
    <string name="day_24">day 24</string>
    <string name="day_25">day 25</string>
    <string name="day_26">day 26</string>
    <string name="day_27">day 27</string>
    <string name="day_28">day 28</string>
    <string name="day_29">day 29</string>
    <string name="day_30">day 30</string>
    <string name="content_desc_1">"Set the bird\'s wings with gold and it will never again soar in the sky."- Rabindranath Tagore.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_2">"I like the sky. You can look at it forever and never get tired of it, and when you don't want to look at it anymore, you stop."- Haruki Murakami.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_3">"There is one spectacle grander than the sea, that is the sky; there is one spectacle grander than the sky, that is the interior of the soul."- Victor Hugo.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_4">"The sky is filled with stars, invisible by day."- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_5"> "Clouds come floating into my life, no longer to carry rain or usher storm, but to add color to my sunset sky."- Rabindranath Tagore.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_6">"I am inspired by anything beautiful. Sometime it's a pair of eyes or flowing gorgeous hair, other times it's the sky or a sunset."- Nadine Velazquez.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_7">"Rest is not idleness... watching the clouds float across the sky, is by no means a waste of time."- John Lubbock.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_8">"You'll never find a rainbow if you're looking down." — Charlie Chaplin</string>
    <string name="content_desc_9">"Try to be a rainbow in someone's cloud." — Maya Angelou</string>
    <string name="content_desc_10">"There's always been a rainbow hanging over your head." — Kacey Musgraves</string>
    <string name="content_desc_11">“Somewhere over the rainbow, skies are blue, and the dreams that you dare to dream really do come true.” — E.Y. Young</string>
    <string name="content_desc_12"> "And still, after all this time,The sun never says to the earth,'You owe Me.'
        Look what happens with A love like that,It lights the Whole Sky."- Hafiz.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_13"> "If you surround yourself with positive people who build you up, the sky is the limit."- Joel Brown.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_14"> "Don't tell me the sky's the limit when there are footprints on the moon."- Paul Brandt.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_15"> "The number of ways you can live in one lifetime is limitless. So why limit yourself? The sky is not the limit. Beyond the universe is."- Suzy Kassem.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_16">A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new. </string>
    <string name="content_desc_17">"Summertime is always the best of what might be." — Charles Bowden.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_18">"Keep your face to the sun and you will never see the shadows." — Helen Keller.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_19">“If there is magic on this planet, it is contained in water.” </string>
    <string name="content_desc_20">"Water is the driving force of all nature."</string>
    <string name="content_desc_21">"Nothing is softer or more flexible than water, yet nothing can resist it.” </string>
    <string name="content_desc_22">"Best Investment on earth is earth"</string>
    <string name="content_desc_23"> "The sky takes on shades of orange during sunrise and sunset, the colour that gives you hope that the sun will set only to rise again."- Ram Charan.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_24">"Only from the heart can you touch the sky."- Rumi.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_25">"When the sun rises, it rises for everyone."</string>
    <string name="content_desc_26">"He was pointing at the moon, but I was looking at his hand."- Richard Siken.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_27">“Thousands have lived without love, not one without water.” </string>
    <string name="content_desc_28">Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_29">“We forget that the water cycle and the life cycle are one.”</string>
    <string name="content_desc_30"> “Only from the heart can you touch the sky.”</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less image quotes.</string>
</resources>